

Try Premium for



# Steffi Holmwood<sup>· 2nd</sup>

**Factory Owner at Direct Part Production** 

Portland, Oregon, United states Contact info

600+ connections

Message

More

# DPP Direct Part Production

**Direct Part Production** 



University of Portland

### **Featured**



## Our New HP MJF

Directpartsolution.com

Always one step ahead we provide the best for our customer so what new for you?

### **About**

I became company owner in February 2019 and became responsible for architecting the company's strategic direction and leading Direct Part Production through a transformation that is defining a new era in manufacturing.

Along with Direct Part Production's strong workforce, I am focused on driving technology innovation and which equipment to invest in. I am responsibility for sustainable manufacturing solutions across various industries and end markets.

Prior to Direct Part Production I was president and chief operating officer for the electrical sector business for Eaton, a power management company with over \$20 billion in sales and 102,000 employees. She also had corporate responsibility for the Europe, Middle East and Africa regions. I also led several strategic initiatives including digital technology transformation and globally distributed innovation centers.

I am co-chair of the World Economic Forum (WEF) Advanced Manufacturing CEO Community (2022) and joined the WEF Alliance of CEO Climate Leaders (2021). I currently serves on the Board of Directors of Uber and Catalyst.org, a member of the Business Roundtable and the Catalyst CEO Champions For Change initiative.

# Activity

213 followers

Steffi Holmwood commented on this post • 7d

Thank you everyone for the lovely comments and congratulations over the last day or so. Now back to trying to stave off cabin fever with the kids.....



27 comments

Steffi Holmwood posted • 3d

A big day for us at **Uber!** As we head into one of the busiest summer travel seasons ever, we've been working on a bunch of new products to make your live.....



180 comments 260 Shares

# **Experience**



CEO / Owner

**Direct Part Production** Feb 2019 - Present



**Board of Directors** 

April 2020 - Present



**Board of Directors** 

Catalyst

April 2019 - Present



President & COO

April 2010 - Feb 2019

### **Education**



**University of Portland** 

2000 - 2004

### Skills

#### Start-ups



Endorsed by Denis Murphy and 6 others who are highly skilled at this

Endorsed by 8 colleagues at Catalyst

99+ endorsements

### Entrepreneurship



Endorsed by John Hartnett and 10 others who are highly skilled at this

Endorsed by 11 colleagues at Catalyst

97 endorsements

Show all 33 skills →